本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： Eraugus  大力  红鼻子的UFO  Yatamisaki  YU  熊猫大虾  Virus Killer
校对/后期： iamazed
机器之心
第一季  第二集
这是2048年
The year is 2048.
不断发展的科技渐渐不受管束
Evolving technologies can no longer be regulated.
危险的高新技术永久地改变了犯罪的领域
Dangerous advancements forever alter the criminal landscape.
警察措手不及
Police are not prepared.
为与这种罪恶抗争 执法机关采用了新型防御武器
Law enforcement combats this corruption with a new line of defense...
但这些武器并不全然相同
but not all are created equal.
DRN的设计初衷是让其尽可能的和人类接近
The idea behind the DRNs was to be as human as possible.
他们是基于一个叫人造灵魂的项目而开发
They were based on a program called Synthetic Soul.
这是疯了的那款吧
That's one of the crazy ones.
- 我带你去 - 我们走
- I'll lead you in? - Let's go.
现在所有的警察
Now all cops...
人类联手人造人一起战斗 保护人民
human and manmade together... take on the battle to watch over us all.
你太棒了
You are incredible.
咱们再找点乐子
Let's get more comfortable, hmm?
好不好
That okay?
紧张吗
You nervous?
你好像心事重重的
It seems like you've got a lot on your mind.
我...没错
Actually... I do.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
- 我通过了所有测试 没问题的 - 麻烦你配合
- I've passed all my tests. I'm clean. - Would you mind?
这不疼的
This won't hurt.
你不必做你不想做的事
You don't have to do anything if you don't want to.
人们来找我的理由千奇百怪
People come to me for all sorts of reasons.
有的人只想聊聊 或者求拥抱
Some want to talk or just to be held.
我们为什么就不能找点乐子呢
Look, why don't we just have some fun?
人们千方百计地寻找联系
People look for connections in different ways.
寻找关心他们的人
Someone who cares about them.
安德烈
Andrei!
看看这个
最后一个
Last one.
我保证
I promise.
穿上衣服
Get dressed.
楼上的现场勘查员完事了吗
CSI finished upstairs?
马上好了 长官
Shouldn't be long, sir.
你是机器人
You're a bot.
对 没错
Yes, I am.
厉害 你能做什么
Cool! What can you do?
哇 帅呆了
Whoa. Oh, awesome!
你也是机器人吗
Are you a robot, too?
不 我是人类
No, I'm human.
那你能做什么
Oh. What can you do?
看好了
Watch this.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
这不痛的 我这条...这条腿是仿生的
It doesn't hurt. I got... I got a synthetic leg!
我没当过小孩都知道你那样做很吓人
I haven't even been a child, and I know that would scare one.
你脑子坏了吗
What's the matter with you?
你这是负能量 伙计
You have negative energy, man.
我能量正得很
My energy's great.
- 你怎么不喜欢小孩呢 - 我没说不喜欢
- Why don't you like kids? - I never said I don't like kids.
这是你说的
You said I don't like kids.
小孩能感知电磁场 约翰
Children can sense electromagnetic fields, John.
- 什么乱七八糟的 - 他们能感知不适 沮丧及负能量
- That's a bunch of baloney. - They can sense discomfort, frustration and bad energy.
猫也一样
As do felines.
你肯定也不喜欢猫吧 对不对
I bet you have an issue with cats, too, am I right?
嘿 我喜不喜欢猫不关你的事
Hey. My issue with cats is none of your business.
我对猫过敏
I'm allergic to cats.
也许是猫对你过敏呢
Maybe the cats are allergic to you.
你想过这没有
You ever consider that?
受害者名叫塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯
Victim is ID'd as Sebastian Jones.
房间是用现金付款的
He paid for the room with cash.
前台说他和一个女人在一起 红头发 二十多岁
Front desk said he showed up with a woman. Red hair, 20s.
大概半小时以后 两个男人来了
About a half hour later, two men showed up.
没留下指纹
There are no fingerprints.
法医那里应该查不出什么线索
I don't think we're gonna get anything from Forensics.
这里的一切都被污染了
Everything is tainted in here.
他们用了DNA炸弹
They used a DNA bomb.
我讨厌那玩意儿
I hate that stuff.
周围涂有吸收剂 第三代
Absorption round, third gen.
不会发出一点声音 这些人是行家
Wouldn't have made a sound. These guys are good.
有监控吗
Any surveillance?
她晚上六点十五分进来
She came in at 6:15 p.m.
他们在二十分钟后抵达
They arrived 20 minutes later.
他们头戴闪光面具
They're wearing FlashMask.
他们拿走了他的包
They took his bag.
约翰
John.
她是机器人
She's an android.
受害者有什么信息
What do we have on our victim?
塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯是一个高端性爱机器人制造商
Sebastian Jones was a high-end sex trade bot-maker.
真可惜他死了
Yeah, too bad he's dead.
否则能给你造个女朋友
Could've made you a girlfriend.
在约会网站有交友信息的人可不是我
I'm not the one with the online dating profile.
我没写过什么交友信息啊
I don't have an online dating profile.
现在有了
You do now.
"摩羯座 喜危险"
"Capricorn who loves danger."
好啊 既然你正写着呢 不如给我加上
Okay. While you're at it, why don't you put down.
"近期遭遇重大车祸并丧偶"
"Recently lost partner in tragic freeway accident."
伙计们 有什么进展
Guys, what do we have?
塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯的公司叫做奥瑞立安智人
Sebastian Jones' company is called Orillian Sapients.
专注于生产高端性爱机器人
They specialize in advanced sexual robotics.
她是产品之一吗
Is this one of his sexbots?
不知道
We don't know.
性爱机器人都有注册牌照
Sexbots are licensed.
它注册给谁了
Who's it registered to?
没有注册人
It's not registered to anybody.
它肯定有主人 一定有注册信息
Someone owns it. It has to be registered.
还有什么关于他的资料
What else do we know about his life?
没有妻子 没有孩子 没有前科
No spouse, no kids, no criminal record.
是个合法商人
Legitimate businessman.
还是个发明家
Inventor.
他名下拥有二十三项专利
He has 23 patents to his name
被誉为模拟人类羞愧反应领域的先锋
and is credited as a pioneer in developing the artificial blush response.
这座城市里的每个男士都欠着这位邪恶天才一屁股帐
Every red-blooded man in this city owes a debt to this fallen genius.
为什么 就因为他制造性爱机器人
Why, because he makes sex trade bots?
他们称之为"机器炮友" 他们很是喜欢
Call 'em "bang bots." They actually like it.
这是你的经验之谈吗
And you know this from experience?
让你说的好像这是件坏事一样
You say it like it's a bad thing.
自从性爱机器人出现后 有关性交易的犯罪下降了38%
Crimes in the sex trade are down 38% since the bots were introduced.
是吧 挺划算的
Right? Do that math.
理查德 被你祸害的真女人越少 世界才能更美好
The fewer real women that have to sleep with you, Richard, the better off the world is.
行了 关于他还知道些什么
Okay. What else do we know about him?
塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯无力偿还他的债务
Sebastian Jones couldn't pay his bills.
三个月前奥瑞立安智人宣布破产
Orillian Sapients declared bankruptcy three months ago.
债主收走了他所有的资产
Creditors seized all of his assets,
目前全部放在一个储存仓库里
and now they're currently sitting in a repo storage facility.
找到一张法院传票
Found a court summons.
塞巴斯蒂安被起诉过
Sebastian was being sued.
肯尼思
Kennex.
这案子有点不对劲
Your case just got weird.
我刚刚发给你 收到了吗
I just sent you something. You get it?
嗯 收到了
Yeah, I got it.
现场勘查员在调查酒店电梯时
The CSIs went through the elevator at the hotel,
扫描了这些人可能接触过的地方 试图提取些DNA样本
scanning spots these guys likely touched, trying to pick up some DNA on them.
- 然后呢 - 我们从那些人身上没找到任何DNA
- Yeah. - We didn't find any DNA on the guys,
但是找到了一些别的
but we found something else.
这是他们找到的第一个指纹样本
That's the first sample they pulled.
她触摸过的所有地方提取的DNA
Everywhere she touched, there was DNA
均来自一名叫妮可・布鲁姆奎斯特的二十五岁女子
from a 25-year-old girl named Nicole Bloomquist,
她三周前在停车场遭人绑架
who was abducted three weeks ago from a parking garage.
你是说我们在找的性爱机器人所留下的DNA
Are you telling me the sexbot we're looking for
是属于这个女孩的
is leaving this girl's DNA?
目前来看是这样
It seems that way.
怎么会
How?
是啊 怎么会呢
Correct. How?
啊 好了
Ah, there you go.
很好 很好
Perfect, perfect.
看看你 动来动去的小怪物
Oh, look at you. Wriggle monster.
好了
Okay.
妈妈帮你拿这个
Mommy'll take it then.
擦擦你的手 擦擦你的脸
Give me your hands, give me your face.
真漂亮
Beautiful.
又发生了一起绑架案
Another abduction happened.
跟妮可・布鲁姆奎斯特的案子一样
Same M.O. as Nicole Bloomquist.
二十多岁 女性 案发地是停车场
20-something female, parking structure.
监控摄像头坏了 没有留下关于绑架的任何录像
Cameras were disabled. There's no surveillance of the abduction.
我还找到了三起和这个案子类似的人口失踪案
And I found three more missing persons cases with the same pattern.
这么说 他们关了摄像头 绑架了那个女人
So, they kill the cams and then take the women.
是 不过这次有所不同 他们漏了一个
Yeah, except this time, something was left behind.
他叫维克多 当时在车里
He was in the car. His name is Victor.
我可以和他聊聊吗
Can I talk to him?
还是我去吧
Maybe I should talk to him.
- 他不太会和孩子打交道 - 嘿
- He's not good with kids. - Hey.
- 还有猫 - 胡说...胡...
- Or cats. - That-That's not...
我跟孩子很处得来 真的
I'm great with kids, really.
嗨
Hey.
我是肯尼思警官
I'm Detective Kennex.
你应该就是维克多 对吗
You must be, uh, Victor, right?
维克多是...是个好名字
Victor's a-a good name.
是个强大 无所畏惧的名字
It's a good, strong name.
Victor本意是胜利者
听着 我知道这一定很难面对
Look, I know this must be hard...
但是我需要你勇敢起来
but I need you to be brave.
好吗
Okay?
你必须要告诉我你妈妈出了什么事
I really need you to tell me what happened with your mom.
你喜欢这个
You like him?
你想要我可以送给你
I'll give him to you if you want him.
但是你要向我保证会好好照顾他
But you got to promise me to look after him
因为他对我来说意义重大
because he means a lot to me.
- 我保证 - 你保证
- I promise. - You promise?
好的
Okay.
我相信你
I trust you.
听着 维克多
Look, Victor.
我真的很需要你的帮助
But I really need your help.
你要告诉我到底发生了什么
Need you to tell me what happened with your mom.
你们当时在车里 对吗
You guys were in a car, right?
你妈妈出去了
Your mom got out.
她去扔垃圾
She went to put the trash away.
然后发生了什么
Then what happened?
我看到一辆车
I saw the car.
你看到谁在车里了吗
Did you see who was in it?
两个男人
Two men.
Two men?
然后发生了什么
What happened then?
车开走了
The car drove away.
是什么样的车什么颜色
What kind of car was it? What color?
是一辆很大的银色的车
It was a big, silver car.
很大的银色的车
A big, silver car.
棒极了
That's good.
我妈妈什么时候来
When is my mom coming?
嘿 维克多
Hey, Victor.
你做的很好
You did really good.
- 怎么了 - 现场勘查员通过录像在车库旁边的街区
- What's up? - CSI found the silver sedan on a traffic cam
发现了那辆银色轿车
a block from the parking structure.
它的车牌是属于一辆红色越野车的
The license plates tracked back to a red SUV.
他们用的是偷来的车牌
They're using stolen plates.
我们动用城市中所有车牌扫描仪寻找那些车牌
We got every plate scanner in the city looking for those tags.
我们会找到那辆车的
We'll find that car.
好的 两个女孩都被相同的手法绑架
Okay, two girls were abducted with the same M.O.
而其中一个的DNA在塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯被杀时
and one of them, her DNA was found on the sexbot
和他在一起的性爱机器人上找到
who was with Sebastian Jones when he was murdered.
我想我们应该寻找那个
I think we should focus on finding
和塞巴斯蒂安在一起的性爱机器人
the sexbot that was with Sebastian.
如果我们可以获取她的记忆
If we can access her memory,
我们也许能看到那天晚上酒店里到底发生了什么
we might be able to see what happened in the hotel that night.
还可以确定是谁做的
And identify who did it.
这是寻找两名失踪者最好的办法
That's our best bet for finding the missing women.
诸位 我有了新线索
Guys, I might have a new angle.
我细查了你们找到的这些传票
I dug into those summonses you found.
塞巴斯蒂安以前的生意伙伴洛伦佐・肖
Sebastian's former business partner Lorenzo Shaw
曾起诉他侵犯知识产权
was suing him for intellectual property infringement
还有他刚在市中心开了一家性爱机器人展销厅
and he just opened a sexbot showroom downtown for himself...
他有动机 他或许参与了这事
it's motive. He could be involved.
去查查他
Check him out.
刚才你和那孩子相处的异常融洽 约翰
You were surprisingly good with that kid back there, John.
尽管你用长颈鹿贿赂他
Even though you had to bribe him with a giraffe.
多谢夸奖
Thanks.
你觉得他妈妈还活着吗
Do you think his mother is still alive?
希望如此
I hope so.
每过一小时 她活着被我们找到的机会就减少一分
Every hour she's gone diminishes the chance of us finding her alive.
如果有人死了 你会怎么告诉一个小孩
What do you tell a small child when someone dies?
我从来没想过这个 你会怎么跟小孩讲
I've never considered that what you would tell a small child.
和对成年人说的话一样
Well, you say the same thing that you'd say to an adult.
对他们怎么说
What do they say?
你告诉他们死去的人
You tell them that the person that died
去了更美好的地方
has gone to a better place.
为什么他们会这么说
Why would anyone say that when there's no way
没人知道活着的东西死了之后会去哪
to really know where living things go when they stop living?
这是为了给他们希望和安慰
It's designed to give hope and comfort.
减轻痛苦
To ease the pain.
人们相信是因为他们必须相信
People believe it because they need to.
我的研究数据表明
Hmm, the data I've studied suggests
证明一个人存在过的最好方式是
that the best proof of one's existence
在他们死去后有人会纪念他们
is if one is remembered after they're gone.
有人告诉过你搭档的儿子
Was your partner's son told that his father
他爸爸去了更美好的地方吗
went to a better place?
我不知道
I don't know.
你从没跟你搭档的儿子讲过话吗
You never spoke to your partner's son?
我理解你为什么会觉得这事很难面对
I can understand why that would be hard for you.
你们把我儿子怎么了
What did you do with my son?
别担心
Don't worry.
现在相关机构会管他的
The authorities will have him by now.
你看 我们...我们不是坏人
You see, we're... we're not monsters.
我有钱 你想要什么都可以 我什么都给你
I have money! Anything you want, anything. I'll give you anything.
求你 我就想见我的儿子
Please, I just want to see my son...
我已经有了
I already have
我想要的东西
what I want.
不 不 不
No, no, no!
你的前生意伙伴
Your ex-partner,
塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯
Sebastian Jones,
你最后一次见他是什么时候
when was the last time you saw him?
半年前 还是七个月前
Six months? Seven?
我们最近闹翻了
We'd been sort of on the outs lately.
"闹翻了"
"On the outs"?
你起诉他了
You were suing him.
我对我们在奥利瑞安一起改进的作品有知识产权
I have intellectual property rights on designs we developed together at Orillian.
既然塞巴斯蒂安裸了 知识产权会发生什么变化
What happens to the I.P. rights now that Sebastian's naked?
我的意思是"死了"
Um, I mean "dead."
现在塞巴斯蒂安死了 知识产权有什么变化
Now that Sebastian's dead. What happens to the I.P. rights?
它们自然归给我了
Well, they would naturally revert to me.
这是你做的模型吗
Is this one of your models?
不 她不是我的
No, she's not mine.
那这个呢
What about this one?
还有这个
Or this one?
你之前见过这些女人吗
You ever seen these women before?
没有 但她们不是人造人
No, but they're not synthetics.
- 你怎么这么肯定 - 我是做这行的
- How can you be sure? - In my line of work,
自然明白
you get to know.
我有很长一段时间没见到你这种型号了
You know, I haven't seen one of you in a while.
最新的性爱机器人加入了一点你的老技术
The latest sexbots have a little bit of your old tech in them.
她们能和她们的服务对象
They're capable of bonding empathetically
建立情感纽带
with their clients.
能感受他们的心情
Sense their moods...
然后作出相应的反应
and respond accordingly.
这是个重大的成就
It's a significant achievement.
如果你的机器人这么特别
If your bots are so special,
为什么塞巴斯蒂安会债务缠身
why was Sebastian so in debt?
如果你认识塞巴斯蒂安 你就会明白
Well, if you knew Sebastian, you'd understand.
他曾经是个艺术家
He was an artist.
我们一起赚了很多钱
We were making good money.
不过后来他决定发展新业务
But he was determined to create the next line.
要比之前的更好
Better than the last.
他把所有的钱都砸了进去 建设新的工厂
He sunk all our capital into new fabs,
购买器材 编制子系统
tooling, subsystems.
他把整个公司都赌在这上面
He bet the whole company on it.
接着我们最大的客户撤销了与我们的合同
And then our biggest client canceled their contract with us.
让我们措手不及
Took us completely by surprise.
也让我们破产了
Bankrupted us.
你们最大的客户是谁
Who was your biggest client?
如果你不想告诉我 那也没关系
Ah, if you don't want to tell me, that's okay.
我们只要命你交出交易记录
We'll just subpoena your records.
挨个检查它们 顺便让你关几天门就够了
Shut you down for a few days while we go through them.
是一个阿尔巴尼亚的财团
It was an Albanian consortium.
他们说过他们正在撤销中间商
They said they were cutting out the middle man.
你是说他们找到了新的供应商
You mean they found a new supplier?
显而易见
Apparently.
塞巴斯蒂安不相信有人
Sebastian couldn't believe that anyone could build
能作出比我们更好的性爱机器人
a better sexbot than us.
我给你看的第一张图
The first picture I showed you.
她是不是阿尔巴尼亚公司的
Did she belong to the Albanians?
是不是因为她 塞巴斯蒂安那晚在酒店才被杀的
Is she why Sebastian was at the hotel the night he was killed?
我不知道
I wouldn't know.
听着 我不想再谈这些了
Look, I-I don't want to talk about this anymore.
他们威胁你了吗
Did they threaten you?
没有
No...
他们是很好的客户 总是按时付钱
They were good clients. They always paid on time.
我能说的就这么多了
And that's all I'm gonna say about them.
抱歉 我还有顾客
Excuse me. I have customers.
肖先生
Mr. Shaw?
你有没有听说过有人
Have you ever heard of people
把人类DNA嵌入性爱机器人身上
incorporating human DNA into a sexbot?
那是违法的
That's illegal.
我觉得你们应该知道这个
And I think you know that.
你可以说你不喜欢机器人
You can say you don't like robots all you want.
不过你的心跳证明你在撒谎
Your pulse says otherwise.
什么
What?
我说的非常清楚
Precisely.
我想要你侵入肖的顾客网络
I want you to hack into Shaw's customer network.
找到阿尔巴尼亚人
Find the Albanians.
我们不需要许可吗
We don't need a warrant?
的确如此
I agree.
找到了
Got it.
五星好评
Five star rating.
计划是什么
What's the plan?
煽风点火
Stir the pot.
他们在寻找拥有人类DNA的机器人
把手从口袋里拿出来
Hands out of your pockets.
- 你见过这个机器人吗 - 没有
- You seen this bot? - No.
没有吗
No?
- 见过这个机器人吗 - 没有
- Seen that bot? - No, no...
我们测试了所有的机器人
We tested all the bots.
他们都通过了 没问题
They all check out. They're clean.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
没错
Yup.
警官们
Officers.
我是经理 有什么能帮助的吗
I'm the manager. Can I help you?
这是你们这儿的机器人吗
Is this one of your bots?
不是
No.
我们这儿有很多选择 能给你找到一个相像的
We got a great selection here. We can get you pretty close to this one.
我们的机器人全都通过了测试
Our bots have passed all the required tests.
警察还有优惠价
Special rate for cops.
我们喜欢警察
We love cops.
没错
Yeah.
- 我们喜欢警察 - 好的 很好
- We love cops. - Well, great.
如果你答出了我所有的问题
If you answer all of my questions,
我也许会考虑你们的服务
maybe I'll let you get to first base.
你是不是从塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯和洛伦佐・肖那进的货
You ever buy from Sebastian Jones and Lorenzo Shaw?
以前是
We used to.
- 现在不是了 - 为什么
- Not anymore. - Why'd you stop?
我们自产自销
We make our own now.
你们确定其中没有一个长成这样的
And you're sure that's not one of them?
之前说过了
Already said.
约翰
John.
斯特尔警员有话要和我们说
Detective Stahl needs to talk to us.
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, gentlemen.
他的生命特征表明他在撒谎
His vitals suggest that he is lying.
没错
Yup.
也可能是他非常讨厌你
Or he doesn't like you very much.
把他加到小孩和猫的那一栏里
Add him to the list of kids and cats.
我们追踪到那辆银色轿车了
We got a hit for the silver sedan.
就是在停车场绑架克里斯汀・海斯曼的那辆
The one that kidnapped Kristen Haseman in the parking garage.
我们在扫描仪里发现了它的踪迹
We picked it up on a plate scanner.
多利安 你看那辆轿车
Dorian, watch the sedan as it goes
在扫描仪里记录的影像
past the scanner.
他的车牌变了
The license plate changes.
他们用了车牌干扰器
They're using a tag scrambler.
我们也发现了 所以转换成了直接监控录像
Once we realized that, we switched to straight surveillance cams
并且发现它进入了第八大街的一个工业设备厂
and tracked it to an industrial facility off 8th Street.
他们在那干嘛
What were they doing there?
不知道 他们在那呆了二十分钟
I don't know, they were there for 20 minutes,
之后我们就找不到他们了
and then we lost 'em.
好吧 我们三分钟之内赶过去
All right, we're three minutes out.
那是什么东西
What the hell is that?
是克里斯汀・海斯曼吗
Is that Kristen Haseman?
不是人类
It's not human.
是酒店的那个女机器人
This is the android from the hotel.
如果他们是这么对待性爱机器人的
If this is what they're doing to their sexbots,
可以想象他们对抓来的女人会做些什么
imagine what they're doing to the women they've abducted.
漂亮的绿眼瞳
Beautiful green.
他们把颜色调得刚刚好
They really have got the color just right.
这些枪眼就是为了
You see, these shots were targeted
粉碎外皮的继电器和存储中心的
precisely to shatter the cortical relays and storage centers.
他们销毁了她的记忆
They destroyed her memory.
当然了 他们要确保不会有人
Yeah, they wanted to ensure no one
通过她的记忆找到塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯的凶手
could retrieve her recorded memories of Sebastian Jones' murder.
- 这些白化人知道他们在做什么 - 是阿尔巴尼亚人
- These albinos knew exactly what they were doing. - Albanians.
那 那就说的通了
Well, that, that would make more sense.
但她的外壳可能会
But there is a small chance
一定程度上保护她的记忆不受损
that her temporal housing might be intact enough
我们就可以来播放她的声像记忆
to salvage some of her echoic memory.
她可能告诉我们那些人
Uh, she might still be able to tell us
对她做了什么
something about the people that did this.
抱歉 伙计
Apologies, mate.
我做这个的时候通常都是一个人
I'm used to being alone when I do this.
- 你可以不用看 - 没关系
- You might want to look away. - It's fine.
为什么他们要把它的皮肤去掉
Why did they peel its skin off?
显然他们不想我们找到线索
Well, they obviously didn't want us to see that either.
等下
Wait a minute,
酒店的监控器发现
the surveillance footage at the hotel.
她的手留下的是人类DNA
Her hands left traces of human DNA.
你觉得他们绑架这些女的是为了她们的皮肤
You think they're abducting the girls to harvest their skin.
如果使用人类皮肤
If you used human skin,
那你就造出了最好的性爱机器
you'd make the best sex machines on the market.
我想塞巴斯蒂安发现这个方法了 所以他们杀了他
I think Sebastian found out about it. That's why they killed him.
性爱机器 机器炮友
Sex machine, bang bot?
有点目光短浅 对吧
It's a bit myopic, isn't it?
不是每个找性爱机器人的人都是为了性爱
Not everyone who visits a sexbot is looking for sex.
有些人是为了交流
Some people go for the conversation
或是结束了应付某些无事不登门的人之后
or for a sympathetic ear at the end of a long working day
拖着疲惫的步伐
surrounded by people who only ever come to visit
寻找倾听者
when they want something from you.
我只是想说
I'm just saying that, uh,
神经界面很精密
the neural interface is quite sophisticated.
总之 可以看出
Anyway, it appears
他们利用被绑架女子的DNA来制造皮肤
they're growing skin using DNA from the abducted women.
再好的人造皮和真正的皮肤相比还是有很大差距
Well, synthetic skin, as good as it is, is a long way from the real thing.
还需要加入能带来吸引力的
There are pheromones and other biological features
信息素和其他生物特征
that trigger attraction.
找到了
Here it is.
完了 彻底被毁
Sorry, it's too damaged.
如果你想知道这些机器人在哪制造
If you want to know where these bots are coming from,
就要给我一个活着的机器人
I'm going to have to get my hands on a live one.
你懂我的意思
So to speak.
你很安静
You're quiet.
怎么了
What's wrong?
刚才看到鲁迪桌子上的机器人
Just looking at that bot on Rudy's table
让我开始思考
makes me think,
谁会记得我
who is going to remember me?
你是个警察
You're a cop.
你帮助过的人都会记得你
The people you help will remember you,
不管你叫什么
whatever your name is.
说到名字 刚有人回复你的交友信息了 约翰
Speaking of names, someone just responded to your dating profile, John.
我的交友信...我以为你开玩笑的
My dating pro... I thought you were kidding.
不开玩笑 我见过你看那些性爱机器人时的神情
Not kidding... I saw the way you were looking at those sexbots.
你的用户名是
Your profile name is...
理查医生
Dr. Richard.
- 理查医生 - 喜欢乳蛋饼
- Dr. Richard. - Who likes quiche,
- 在沙滩上漫步 听轻柔的爵士乐 - 你不要叫我理查医生了
- long walks on the beach, smooth jazz. - You seriously did not call me Dr. Richard.
我以为你想约个会
I thought you wanted to meet someone.
我约了很多女人了 不需要你的帮助
I meet plenty of women. I don't need your help.
我进行了生物扫描 你的睾丸已经蓄势待发了
I-I ran a bio scan, and it looked like your testicles were at full capacity.
你扫描了我的蛋蛋
You're scanning my balls?
我并不享受那个过程 我只是...
I didn't enjoy it, i just...
- 我的天 疯了 - 我没有办法不注意到你的蠢蠢欲动
- Oh, my God, this is unbelievable. - I can't help but notice you're backed up.
你这是什么毛病
What is the matter with you?
别再扫描我的蛋了
Don't scan my testicles ever again.
知道了
Copy that.
她长什么样
What does she look like?
你希望她什么样
What do you want her to look like?
深情的棕眼睛
Brown eyes, soulful.
身高
Height?
标准就行 我喜欢小麦色皮肤的
Average height. I like brunettes.
你会和同行交往吗
Would you date anyone in your profession
或者说你更喜欢和非同行交往
or would you prefer to date someone outside of it?
都可以
Sure, either way.
我喜欢聪明的女人 比我聪明的女人
I like smart women, you know, women that are smarter than me.
这不难找
That won't be hard.
你知道你刚才描述的就是斯特尔警探 对吧
You are aware that you just described. Detective Stahl, right?
肯尼思
Kennex.
嘿 我们找到你说的银色轿车了
Hey, we got a 20 on the silver sedan you posted.
我刚刚上传给多利安
I just uploaded it to Dorian.
好的 谢啦
Uh, okay, thank you, um,
斯特尔警探 谢啦
Detective Stahl, thanks.
- 好啦 谢谢 斯特尔警探 - 闭嘴
- Okay, thank you, Detective Stahl. - Shut up.
给我闭嘴
Shut it, zip it.
警察
Police!
举起手来 不许动 把手放在仪表盘上
Hands up! Hands on the dash! Don't you move! Put your hands on the dashboard!
抓住他们 别让他们乱动
Hold 'em, keep 'em there!
不许动 赶紧把手放在仪表盘上
Do not move! Put your hands on the dashboard now
- 放到我能看到的地方 - 转过去
- where I can see 'em! - Turn around, turn around!
从车里出来
Step out of the car.
过来
Come on.
到前面来
Around front.
嗨 我是瓦妮莎
Hi, I'm Vanessa.
- 嘿 你好吗 - 我需要一个DNA样本
- Hey, how you doing? - I need to take a DNA sample.
请张开嘴
Open your mouth, please.
为什么
Why?
我已经通过所有测试了
I've passed all my tests.
劳驾
Please.
她的DNA属于罗琳・怀特
Her DNA belongs to a Lorraine White,
她两个月前在圣克莱尔被绑架
abducted from a parking structure two months ago in St. Clair.
实验室
Lab.
鲁迪
Rudy,
给你找了些皮肤
found you some skin.
阿尔巴尼亚人不会告诉我们被绑架的人在哪
The Albanians aren't telling us where the kidnap victims are.
我们得从性爱机器人那里收集信息
We need to get that information from a sexbot.
已经有三个女孩失踪了
We have three missing girls out there
可能还有更多女孩失踪
somewhere, maybe more.
我会尽我所能来解决这个案子
I'll pull everything I can from it.
又见面啦
Hello again.
一个人类的DNA被用来合成你的皮肤
A human's DNA was used to make your skin.
这个女人
This woman.
我们得找到她 时间不多了
We need to find her. We don't have much time.
你以前见过她吗
Have you seen her before?
没
No.
你仔细想想
I need you to think.
这很重要
It's really important.
你见过她吗
Have you seen her?
没
No.
你在哪里生产出来的
Where were you made?
你主人是谁
Who owns you?
你知道你在哪里出生的吗
Do you know where you were born?
你跟这个女孩工作过吗
You ever worked with this girl?
沙琳
Charlene.
是的 沙琳
Right, Charlene.
你知道她在哪出生的吗
Do you know where she was born?
你们的主人是谁
Who owns you?
她可能不太理解这些词
She's probably not conscious of those terms.
今晚这些人要把你带去什么地方
Where were those men taking you tonight?
他们想载我一程
They were taking me for a ride.
我们认为他们载你是想要毁掉你
We think they were taking you to be destroyed.
为什么有人想要毁掉我
Why would anybody want to destroy me?
跟我在一起有好多好多乐子可享受呢
There are much, much better things to do with me.
如果你不愿意的话 我们可以什么都不做
We don't have to do anything if you don't want to.
我很善于倾听
I'm a very, very good listener.
你知道 人们通过不同方式寻求联系
You know, people look for connections in different ways.
但所有人都在寻找的
That's all people are looking for,
就是有人关心他们
is someone who cares about them.
这也是我在这里的原因
That's what I'm here for.
你知道沙琳在哪吗
Do you know where Charlene is?
知道
Yes.
我能见她吗
Can I see her?
为什么你要见她
Why do you want to?
我不知道
I don't know.
你被设计来跟人们建立联系
You were designed to bond with people.
这是你的使命
That's what you were developed to do.
即察觉他们的存在
To notice when they're there.
也就是说他们不在的时候你也能察觉到
That also means you notice when they're not there.
这就是你要见她的原因
That's why you want to see her.
就是你的感觉
That's what you're feeling.
是谁让你跟今晚我们找到的那些人走的
Who told you to go with the men we found you with tonight?
尤里
Yuri.
你认识尤里吗
Do you know Yuri?
认识 我们认识
Yeah, we know Yuri.
我去楼上
I'm going upstairs.
闪开
Move!
该走了
什么都不要带
摧毁实验室
她们会死的
她们还能生长很多皮肤
我们会在别处再建一个实验室
快点走
你先走
You go first.
他们不在这儿
They're not here.
这不是那栋楼
This isn't the right building.
办公室也是空的
Office is empty, too.
我想我能找到皮肤实验室
I think I can find the skin lab.
鲁迪
Rudy?
怎么了 多利安
Yes, Dorian?
这些性爱机器人大部分是建立在
Most of these sexbots are platformed
旧的尤朱诺悬挂式学习模块的平台上
on an old UJuno Pendant Learning Module.
是啊 自从我们停止在DRN上使用它们之后
Uh, yeah, uh, those modules were available to the public sector
那些模块就对公众开放了
once we stopped using them on the DRNs.
问题在于它们会发出多余的GPS信号
Problem was that they were giving off an unwanted GPS signal.
是啊 这是个烦人的副作用
Yeah, it was an unwanted side effect.
每当它们自动更新它们的软件时
Um, whenever they, uh, automatically updated their software,
就会不经意发出信号
they'd inadvertently send out a signal
这样那些想找到你的人就有路可循了
allowing those so inclined to, uh, track you.
那个东西有没有日志
Is there a log of that?
我想一定有
I'm sure there is.
你能不能进入瓦妮莎内部的GPS日志
Can you access Vanessa's internal GPS log
来找出那个模块第一次发出信号的时间
to find the very first time that the module sent a signal?
这是可实现的
It's possible.
如果我们能发现她第一次被激活的时间
If we can find out the first time she was activated,
- 我们就能找到... - 找到她的出生地点
- we can find... - Find out where she was born.
那个皮肤实验室
The skin lab.
好了 请耐心点
All right, bear with me.
不会太久的
It won't be a minute.
瞧瞧这个
Oh. Look at that.
那是我的充电器 用来... 不重要啦
That's the charger for my... doesn't matter.
我们开始吧
Um, here we go.
我需要的就是这个
This is the one I need.
好吧 你好
right. Uh, hello.
我需要进入你的数据端口
I need to access your data port.
听上去有点粗鲁
That sounds rude. Um,
我需要插入我的... 更难听了
I need to insert my... Oh, that's even worse.
哦 真友好
Um... Oh, friendly.
我向你保证 这跟性无关
Um, it's nothing sexual, I assure you.
倒不是说性有什么不好的
Not that there's anything wrong with sex.
我是说 谁不喜欢性呢
I mean, who doesn't like sex?
反正我喜欢
Not me.
我是说 我喜欢 这才是重点
I mean, I do. That's-that's the point.
但那样的话 至少是不太恰当
But that would be, um, inappropriate at best.
我保证 这不会痛的
This is not gonna hurt, I promise you.
这就好
There we go.
好吧
right.
让我
Just, um...
看一看你的...
having a look at your, uh...
数据
...statistics.
看起来你是在金斯敦高地第一次被激活的
Looks like you were first activated in Kingston Heights.
安全
Clear!
把他干掉
Take him out!
不要
No!
快点 快点
Move it! Move it!
- 丢掉武器 快丢掉 说你呢 - 丢掉武器
- Drop that weapon! Drop it, you! - Drop the weapon!
不要开枪
Don't shoot!
趴到地上 快
On the ground! Now!
安全
Clear!
- 安全 - 安全
- Clear. - Clear!
安全
Clear!
- 这是罗琳・怀特 - 她死了
- This is Lorraine White. - She's deceased.
她是布鲁姆奎斯特 她还活着
Call Bloomquist. She's still alive.
克里斯汀・海斯曼 她还活着
Kristen Haseman... she's alive.
维克多见到你会很高兴的
Victor is gonna be very happy to see you.
干得好
Great work.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 你应该庆祝一下 - 他会的
- You should celebrate. - He will.
你有一个约会
You have a date.
什么
What?
不 我没有
No, I don't.
你有的 和约会网站上的那个女人
Yes, you do... with the woman from the dating web site.
什么 没有
Wha...? No.
他的资料非常棒
He has a wonderful profile.
她会在七点钟等你
She's expecting you at 7:00.
那是...
That's a...
那只是个...玩笑 我能泡到很多女人
it's just a... it's a joke, you know. I get a lot of women.
- 我不是说很多 就... - 不管怎么说 你应该庆祝一下
- I mean, not a lot... you know, just... - You should celebrate no matter what.
祝你今晚约会愉快
Have a great night... on your date.
谢谢
Thanks.
晚安
Good night.
你这个机器叛徒又插我刀
Benedict Android strikes again.
典故自Benedict Arnold 美国独立战争时期的著名叛徒
- 我今晚不能去约会 - 为什么
- I can't go on a date tonight. - Why?
因为我已经有想去见的人了
Because I've already got someone I want to see.
- 但约翰  如果你... - 你完成你的报告了吗
- But, John, if you just... - Do you have your report done?
是的 快完成了
Uh, yeah, almost.
销毁机器人的时候 我们需要个体的证明
We'll need individual certificates when the bots are destroyed.
- 好吗 - 好的
- Okay? - Okay.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们不能允许有人类DNA的机器人存在
We can't have bots with human DNA.
她必须被销毁
She has to be deactivated.
但是你们做的很好 确实很好
But well done. Very well done.
- 谢谢你 - 明天见
- Thank you. - See you tomorrow.
你还好吗
You okay?
我想去看看
I'd like to be there.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我要去哪里
Where am I going?
去一个更好的地方
To a better place.
你会去那里吗
Will you be there?
我会记得你的
I will remember you.
马蒂
Marty,
你还记得约翰・肯尼思吗
do you remember John Kennex?
他以前是你爸爸的搭档
He was your dad's partner.
我想和你聊聊你的父亲
I want to tell you about your father.
驾驶证 姓名: 塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯
资料搜索
塞巴斯蒂安 琼斯
法院传票
被告人: 塞巴斯蒂安・琼斯
机器人制造商与前合作伙伴闹上法庭
新型性爱机器人已发布
接入网络中
搜索 阿尔巴尼亚
心率升高
信息识别
结果: 匿名性爱机器人
发现匹配信息
罗琳 怀特
识别芯片
金斯敦高地